Register of the William T. Poole collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Un-American Activities Subject File, 1920-1976 (Box 51-231.)
  - Pacifica Foundation. Printed announcement, 1966 (Folder 164: 2)
  - Palo Alto Peace Club [Palo Alto, California]. Serial issues (Flashlight), and pamphlet (Report on the Japanese Peace Treaty), 1951-1956 (Folder 164: 3)
  - Parmalee, Patty. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 164: 4)
  - Party of Progressive Socialist Workers. Leaflets, ca. 1971 (Folder 164: 5)
  - Pauling, Linus. Printed articles, 1965 (Folder 164: 6)
  - Peace (General). Material is overwhelmingly from the Vietnam War era. (Folder 164)
    See also Anti-draft movement (General), GI dissidents (General), and Audiovisual File
    - Issuances of miscellaneous and unidentified peace organizations (Folder 164)
    - General. Leaflets, flyers, circular letters, circulars, press releases, programs, printed appeals, and announcements, 1950-1974 (Folder 164: 7-9)
    - General (contd.) (Folder 165: 1-2)
    - Serial issues, bulletins, and newsletters, 1962-1973 (Folder 165: 3)
    - Pamphlets (A Handbook on the War in Asia; In the Belly of the Dinosaurs; Leadership and World Society; Non-Violent Action: How It Works; Testing and Taming of Nuclear Weapons; This May Happen to You; Vietnam: A Thousand Years of Struggle), 1960-1972 (Folder 165: 4)
    - Internal documents. Manuals, memoranda, letters, and meeting programs and agenda, 1965-1972 (Folder 165: 5)
    - (Folder 165)
    - Mailing and contact lists, 1965-1973. (Folder 166: 1)
      Includes accompanying HISC memoranda and photocopies of documents supplied by informant
    - Material about peace organizations (Folder 166)
      - HUAC/HISC documents. Press releases, memoranda, and notes, 1965-1973. (Folder 166: 2)
        Includes material related to bill proposed by HUAC to punish obstruction of Armed Forces
      - Other governmental documents. Congressional and other speeches, proposed bills, press releases, and printed Senate Internal Security Subcommittee staff study (The Anti-Vietnam Agitation and the Teach-In Movement), 1965-1974 (Folder 166: 3)
      - Miscellany. Deposition of Sharon Stewart, and typescript reports of unknown authorship on peace movement, especially in Cleveland area, 1967-1971 (Folder 166: 4)
      - Clippings, 1963-1973 (Folder 166: 5)
      - Clippings, 1963-1973 (contd.) (Folder 167: 1-2)
      - Printed articles and mainstream serial issues, 1961-1973 (Folder 167: 3)
      - Booklets (Authors Take Sides on Vietnam; Images of Our Times [pictorial]), 1967-1971 (Folder 167: 4)
  - Peace Action Council of Southern California. (Folder 167)
    Includes People's Action Union for Peace and Justice, and Student Union for Peace and Justice
    - General. Circular letters, minutes, memoranda, flyers, and leaflets, 1967-1974 (Folder 167: 5)
    - Peace and Justice. Serial issues, 1971-1974 (Folder 167: 6)
    - Mailings. Mailing list, and mailings received, 1971-1974 (Folder 168: 1)
  - Peace and Freedom Party. Circulars, flyers, list of endorsers, serial issues (Peace and Freedom News), clippings, and printed articles, 1967-1969 (Folder 168: 2)
  - Peace and Justice Fund '71. Circular letters, 1971 (Folder 168: 3)
  - Peace Book Company [Hong Kong]. Catalog, 1966 (Folder 168: 4)
  - Peace-Keeping Ways and Means Committee. Printed appeals, 1966 (Folder 168: 5)
  - Peace/Rights Organizing Committee [University of California, Berkeley]. Leaflet, flyers, and clippings, 1966 (Folder 168: 6)
  - Peacemaker. Serial issue and flyer, 1967 (Folder 168: 7)
  - Pentagon Papers. Leaflet, circular, Congressional speech, printed article, Pentagon Papers Fund circular letter, and serial issues (Pentagon Paper), 1971-1972 (Folder 168: 8)
  - People's Anti-Fascist Resistance League [Ithaca, New York]. Flyer, 1972 (Folder 168: 9)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission. Circulars, and pamphlets (The Bicentennial Era, 1972-1976: The Tory's Program/The Patriot's Program; Come Home, America), ca. 1972 (Folder 168: 10)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice. (Folder 168)
    See also Peace Action Council of Southern California
    - Correspondence, 1971-1973. (Folder 168: 11)
    - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice issuances (Folder 168)
      - General. Press releases, leaflets, flyers, printed appeal, petitions, and circulars, 1971-1973 (Folder 168: 12)
      - General (contd.) (Folder 169: 1)
      - Movin' Together. Serial issues, 1971-1972 (Folder 169: 2)
      - Training manual, 1971 (Folder 169: 3)
      - Internal documents. Minutes, memoranda, position papers, proposals, notes, and mailing and contact lists, 1971-1973. (Folder 169: 4)
        Includes documents submitted by organizations working within the Coalition
    - Material about the People's Coalition for Peace and Justice (Folder 169)
      - General. Clippings, printed articles, and Congressional speech, 1971-1973 (Folder 169: 5)
      - HISC memoranda, together with accompanying People's Coalition for Peace and Justice exhibit documents, 1971-1974 (Folder 170: 1)
  - People's Fund [Washington, D.C.]. Printed appeal, 1971 (Folder 170: 2)
  - People's Party [original tentative title New Party]. Circular letters, convention documents, memoranda, proposals, leaflets, serial issues (Grass Roots; Newpaper), and clippings, 1971-1975 (Folder 170: 3)
  - People's Peace Treaty [re Vietnam War]. Proposed text, leaflets, flyers, circulars, petitions, printed articles, and HISC memorandum, 1971-1972 (Folder 170: 4-5)
  - People's Radio Foundation [New York City]. HUAC dossier, including bylaws, list of stockholders, correspondence, report, and leaflet, 1939-1946 (Folder 170: 6)
  - Philadelphia Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 171: 1)
  - Physicians' Forum. Report, 1949 (Folder 171: 2)
  - Pickens, William. Letters, printed announcements, printed articles, and letterhead data, 1938-1940 (Folder 171: 3)
  - Pioneers. Pamphlet (Who Are the Young Pioneers?), ca. 1930s (Folder 171: 4)
  - Pittsburgh Ad Hoc Committee on Vietnam. Printed appeals and clipping, 1966 (Folder 171: 5)
  - Plainfield Joint Defense Committee [Plainfield, New Jersey]. Circular letters, leaflets, and petitions, 1969 (Folder 171: 6)
  - Poland, Jefferson. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 171: 7)
  - Political Affairs Club [University of Hawaii]. Clipping, ca. 1960s (Folder 171: 8)
  - Political Prisoners Bail Fund Committee. Circular letter, 1935 (Folder 171: 9)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund. Letters, circulars, and list of sponsors, 1973 (Folder 171: 10)
  - Pollock, Sam. Photocopy of index card files, 1955-1972 (Folder 171: 11)
  - Poor People's Corporation [Jackson, Mississippi]. Circular letter, 1966 (Folder 171: 12)
  - Portland Committee to End the War in Vietnam [Portland, Oregon]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 171: 13)
  - Portland Draft Resisters' Union [Portland, Oregon]. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 171: 14)
  - Poverty Workers for Peace [Baltimore]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 171: 15)
  - Primack, Maxwell. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 171: 16)
  - Princeton University protests re McCarran Act and Vietnam War. Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 171: 17)
  - Professionals for Peace [San Francisco]. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 171: 18)
  - Progressive. Circular letters, serial issues, and printed article from the journal, 1969-1973 (Folder 171: 19)
  - Progressive Citizens of America (Folder 171)
    - General. Letters, circulars, leaflets, printed appeals, list of endorsers, and financial report, 1947-1948 (Folder 171: 20)
    - Conference on Thought Control in the United States (Beverly Hills, 1947). Program, and booklets reprinting conference proceedings (Folder 171: 21)
    - HUAC dossier, including report and exhibit issuances of Progressive Citizens of America, 1946-1947 (Folder 171: 22)
  - Progressive Labor Party (Folder 171)
    - Progressive Labor Party issuances (Folder 171)
      - General. Constitution, internal bulletin, convention resolutions, circular letters, flyers, and leaflets, 1964-1971. (Folder 171: 23)
        Includes statement by expelled members
      - Challenge. Serial issues and printed articles from the journal (Folder 172)
        - 1964-1969 (Folder 172: 1)
        - 1970-1971 (Folder 172: 2)
      - Marxist-Leninist Quarterly. Serial issues and printed article from the journal, 1964 (Folder 172: 3)
      - Progressive Labor/PL. Serial issues and printed articles from the journal (Folder 172)
        - 1962-1967 (Folder 172: 4)
        - 1968-1969 (Folder 172: 5)
      - Spark. Serial issue and printed article from the journal, 1967 (Folder 172: 6)
      - World Revolution. Serial issue, 1969 (Folder 172: 7)
      - Pamphlets, 1966-1970 (Folder 172)
        - Black Liberation; Black Liberation Now!; Build a Base in the Working Class; District 65 RWDSU AFL-CIO: An Analysis; Don't Be a Sucker!; The Plot against Black America; Pre-Civil War Black Nationalism; Sit-Down (Folder 173: 1)
        - Strike!; Students and Revolution; Trade Union Program; The Truth about Welfare; Vietnam: Defeat U.S. Imperialism!; We Accuse (Folder 173: 2)
    - Material about the Progressive Labor Party (Folder 173)
      - HUAC/HISC documents. Memoranda, staff study, press release, report analyzing Progressive Labor Party Vietnam work-in manual, and exhibit issuances of the Progressive Labor Party, 1965-1969 (Folder 173: 3)
      - HUAC hearing of 1965 June, with testimony of Judith Anne Warden and related exhibits (Folder 173: 4)
      - Legal documents from criminal proceedings re 1964 Harlem riots, 1965-1967 (Folder 173: 5)
      - Clippings and Congressional speech, 1964-1970 (Folder 173: 6)
  - Progressive Party. Correspondence, minutes, nomination certification, press releases, leaflets, flyers, mailing lists, clippings, and printed articles, 1947-1954 (Folder 173: 7)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace. Circular letters, flyers, and leaflets, 1962-1972 (Folder 173: 8)
  - Protest to End the War in Vietnam [Trenton, New Jersey]. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 173: 9)
  - Provisional Committee for Democratic Rights. Petitions to Congress opposing Subversive Activities Control Act (preliminary version of later Internal Security Act [McCarran Act]), 1948 (Folder 174)
    Petition signatures predominantly from New York City area
    - General (Folder 174: 1-4)
    - General (contd.) (Folder 175: 1-4)
    - General (contd.) (Folder 176: 1-4)
    - General (contd.) (Folder 177: 1-2)
    - Signatures collected by identifiable organizations (Folder 177)
      - American Labor Party (Folder 177: 3)
      - Brooklyn Consumers and Tenants Council (Folder 177: 4)
      - Congress of American Women (Folder 177: 5)
      - Department Store Employees Union Local 1250 (Folder 177: 6)
      - International Workers Order (Folder 177: 7)
      - Montana Wallace for President Committee (Folder 177: 8)
      - New York County Communist Party (Folder 177: 9)
      - Ocean Front Tenants League (Folder 177: 10)
      - Progressive Citizens of America (Folder 177: 11)
      - Students for Wallace (Folder 177: 12)
      - Thirteenth Assembly District Wallace for President Committee [New York] (Folder 177: 13)
      - United Auto Workers Union Local 359 (Folder 177: 14)
      - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Union (Folder 178: 1)
      - United Office and Professional Workers Union (Folder 178: 2)
      - United Public Workers Union Local 20 (Folder 178: 3)
      - Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union Local 65 (Folder 178: 4)
  - Psychologists and Psychotherapists Concerned about Vietnam. Circular letters and printed appeals, 1967-1968 (Folder 178: 5)
  - Psychologists Committee on Vietnam. Circular letter and printed appeal, 1965-1967 (Folder 178: 6)
  - Publishers for Peace in Vietnam. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 178: 7)
  - Puerto Rico. Flyers, leaflet, and printed articles re solidarity with people of Puerto Rico, 1967-1973 (Folder 178: 8)
  - Quaker Action Group. Circulars, flyer, press release, clippings, and HUAC memorandum, 1966-1969 (Folder 178: 9)
  - Quakers (General). Includes Friends Civil Liberties Committee. Correspondence, press releases, pamphlets (Friends and the Use of the Fifth Amendment; The Plymouth Meeting Controversy), clippings, Congressional speech, and HUAC and U.S. Department of the Treasury memoranda, 1957-1972 (Folder 178: 10)
  - Queens Committee to End the War in Vietnam [New York City]. Flyers and printed article, 1966 (Folder 178: 11)
  - Rabinowitz, Joni. Amicus curiae brief before U.S. Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals in case of Rabinowitz vs. United States, ca. 1964-1966 (Folder 179: 1)
  - Radical Education Project [Students for a Democratic Society project]. Circular letters, leaflets, printed appeals, study guides, clipping, and HISC memorandum, 1967-1971 (Folder 179: 2)
  - Radical Libertarian Alliance. Serial issue (Abolitionist), 1971 (Folder 179: 3)
  - Radical Student Union [University of California, Berkeley]. Flyer, ca. 1969 (Folder 179: 4)
  - Radical Women's Group [New York City]. Flyers and circulars, 1968 (Folder 179: 5)
  - Radio Free People [New York City]. Circular letter and catalogs, 1970-1971 (Folder 179: 6)
  - Radio Stateside for American Servicemen in South Vietnam [Los Angeles]. Radio broadcast summaries, clippings, printed articles, and HUAC memoranda, 1966 (Folder 179: 7)
  - Radio Writers Guild. Circular letters and report, 1949-1951 (Folder 179: 8)
  - Ramparts. Circular letters, printed appeals, leaflet, Congressional speech, informant's report, clippings, and printed articles, 1966-1971 (Folder 179: 9)
  - Ramsey, Ronald B. Clippings, HUAC memorandum, and photocopy of index card file, 1965-1966. (Folder 179: 10)
    See also Radio Stateside for American Servicemen in South Vietnam
  - Raymond, John. Printed article, 1966 (Folder 179: 11)
  - Red International of Labor Unions. Pamphlet (Social Insurance), ca. 1930s (Folder 179: 12)
  - Redwood City Committee against Napalm [Redwood City, California]. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 179: 13)
  - Reed, David A. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 179: 14)
  - Reed, Dean. Motion picture publicity press release, radio broadcast summary, and clippings, 1966-1971. (Folder 179: 15)
  - Reichstag Fire Trial Anniversary Committee. Printed appeals, 1943 (Folder 179: 16)
  - Religion (General). Leaflets, flyers, circulars, programs, pamphlets (How Liberal Clergymen Aid the Revolutionists; Radicalism; Today's Martyred Church Tortured for Christ), serial issues (Interfaith Reporter; Student Action), clippings, printed articles, reports, Congressional speech, and HUAC memorandum, 1923-1972 (Folder 179: 17)
  - Religious Freedom Committee. Letter, circulars, leaflets, pamphlets (Abolish Congressional Inquisition; Congress and Religious Freedom; A Conspiracy to Destroy Religion; Jesus as a Free Speech Victim), and serial issues (Religious Freedom News), 1960-1968 (Folder 180: 1)
  - Republic of New Africa [Detroit]. Memoranda, circular letter, conference proceedings, clippings, printed article, and HUAC memorandum and chart, 1968-1969 (Folder 180: 2)
  - Resist [re draft]. Circular letters, printed appeals, newsletters, and clippings, 1967-1972 (Folder 180: 3)
  - Resistance [re draft]. Circular letters, leaflets, flyers, printed appeals, newsletters, and clippings, 1967-1969 (Folder 180: 4)
  - Revolutionary Action Movement. Circulars and HUAC memoranda, ca. 1963-1968 (Folder 180: 5)
  - Revolutionary Socialist League. Letter, convention resolution, pamphlet (Chile: Never Again!), and serial issues (Torch), 1973-1974 (Folder 180: 6)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade. Circular and leaflet, 1975 (Folder 180: 7)
  - Revolutionary Union [originally Bay Area Revolutionary Union]. Leaflets, flyers, circulars, serial publication (Red Papers), clippings, printed articles, Congressional speech, and HISC memoranda, 1969-1973 (Folder 180: 8)
  - Revolutionary Workers Committee [Detroit]. Flyer, ca. 1968 (Folder 180: 9)
  - Revolutionary Workers Party (Trotskyist) [Great Britain]. Printed articles, 1963-1970 (Folder 180: 10)
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement II [Students for a Democratic Society]. Flyers and circulars, 1969 (Folder 180: 11)
  - Ring around the Congress [re Vietnam War; Washington, D.C.]. Press release, flyers, leaflets, and circulars, 1972 (Folder 180: 12)
  - Riordon, Dennis M. Letters and clipping, 1967 (Folder 180: 13)
  - Rising Up Angry [Chicago]. Serial issues and HISC memorandum, 1971-1974 (Folder 180: 14)
  - Rodd, Thomas. Circular letter and HUAC memorandum, 1966 (Folder 180: 15)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Presidential reelection campaign, 1944. Campaign literature and clippings (Folder 180: 16)
    See also Independent Voters' Committee of the Arts and Sciences for Roosevelt
  - Roosevelt University antiwar protests. Clippings, 1966-1968 (Folder 180: 17)
  - Russian War Relief. Printed appeal, 1941 (Folder 180: 18)
  - Ruth Gage-Colby Testimonial Committee. Circular letter, 1971 (Folder 180: 19)
  - SENSE: Students for Peace [Pennsylvania State University]. Clippings, 1965 (Folder 181: 1)
  - St. Louis Citizens for Peace in Vietnam. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 181: 2)
  - St. Louis Peace Council. Flyers, proposal, draft news story, and clipping, 1969 (Folder 181: 3)
  - Salisbury, Harrison. Radio broadcast summary and clipping, 1967 (Folder 181: 4)
  - San Diego Peace Forum. Correspondence, flyers, newsletters, contact list, financial records, and HUAC memorandum, 1951-1955 (Folder 181: 5)
    See also Southern California Peace Crusade.
  - San Quentin Six Defense Committee. Letter, petition, pamphlet (The San Quentin Six), and serial issue (Black Scholar), 1974 (Folder 181: 6)
  - Sanders, Beulah. Photocopy of index card file, 1966-1972 (Folder 181: 7)
  - Save Vietnam Community. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 181: 8)
  - Savich, Elisabeth M. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 181: 9)
  - Scales, Junius. Press release, petition, and list of endorsers, 1962 (Folder 181: 10)
  - Scanlan's. Serial issues, 1970 (Folder 181: 11)
  - Scheer, Robert. California Congressional election campaign leaflet and clippings, 1966 (Folder 181: 12)
  - School for Democracy [New York City]. List of lecturers and HUAC memorandum, 1942-ca. 1944 (Folder 181: 13)
  - Science and Society. Serial issues and printed excerpts from the journal (Folder 181)
    - 1938-1952 (Folder 181: 14)
    - 1964-1965 (Folder 181: 15)
  - Scottsboro Defense Committee. Photocopy of pamphlet (4 Free, 5 in Prison), 1937 (Folder 181: 16)
  - Seattle Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 182: 1)
  - Seattle Committee to End Violence in Vietnam. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 182: 2)
  - Seeger, Pete. Printed articles and pamphlet (Pete Seeger [Folk Singer]), 1962-1965 (Folder 182: 3)
  - Sequoia School [Los Angeles]. Catalogs, 1954 (Folder 182: 4)
  - Set the Date Now [re Vietnam War]. Printed appeal, flyers, leaflets, and Washington Interreligious Convocation programs, 1971-1972 (Folder 182: 5)
  - Sexual Freedom League. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 182: 6)
  - Sherman, Ken. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 182: 7)
  - Sifton, Paul. Printed articles and letterhead data, 1934-1938 (Folder 182: 8)
  - Sing-In for Peace Committee [New York City]. Printed appeals, 1965-1966 (Folder 182: 9)
  - Sing Out! (Folder 182)
    - General. Serial issues and circular, 1966-1968 (Folder 182: 10)
    - Booklets (Lift Every Voice!; The People's Song Book), 1948-1953 (Folder 182: 11)
  - 67 for Action [University of Illinois-Chicago Circle]. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 182: 12)
  - Smith, Stephen. Clippings and HUAC memorandum, 1965-1966 (Folder 182: 13)
  - Sobell, Morton. Letters, petitions, lists of enorsers, press release, and amici curiae brief in case of Sobell vs. United States before U.S. Supreme Court, 1954-1960. (Folder 182: 14)
    See also Committee to Free Morton Sobell, and Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell
  - Social Work Today. Serial issue and list of endorsers, 1941-1942 (Folder 182: 15)
  - Social Workers for Peaceful Negotiations [re Vietnam War]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 182: 16)
  - Socialist Anti-War Union [Berkeley]. Flyers, 1967 (Folder 182: 17)
  - Socialist Labor Committee. Flyers and serial issues (Crisis), 1971 (Folder 182: 18)
  - Socialist Labor Party (Folder 182)
    - General. Leaflets, flyers, serial issues (Weekly People), and clippings, 1956-1971 (Folder 182: 19)
    - Pamphlets (The Americanism of Socialism; Militarism; Socialist Industrial Unionism; Socialist Reconstruction of Society; War?Why?), 1951-1955 (Folder 183: 1)
  - Socialist Party (Folder 183)
    - General. Flyers and circulars, 1968-1970 (Folder 183: 2)
    - Serial issues (New America; Socialist Tribune), 1965-1971 (Folder 183: 3)
  - Socialist Revolution. Circular letter, 1969 (Folder 183: 4)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference. Circular letters, printed announcements, printed articles, Congressional speech, and informant's report, 1966-1971 (Folder 183: 5)
  - Socialist Workers Party. (Folder 183)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1973 (Folder 183: 6)
    - Socialist Workers Party issuances (Folder 183)
      - General. Leaflets, flyers, and press catalog, ca. 1961-1974. (Folder 183: 7)
        Includes Militant Labor Forum events
      - Internal documents. Internal bulletins, branch newsletters, and letter by Arne Swabeck, 1966-1973 (Folder 183: 8)
      - Election campaign literature (Folder 183)
        - 1968 (Folder 183: 9)
        - 1972 (Folder 183: 10)
      - Intercontinental Press. Printed articles from the journal, 1971 (Folder 184: 1)
      - International Socialist Review. Serial issues, printed article from the journal, index, and circular, 1970-1971 (Folder 184: 2)
      - Militant (Folder 184)
        - General. Circulars, indexes, and printed articles from the journal, 1963-1974 (Folder 184: 3)
        - Serial issues (Folder 184)
          - 1964-1970 (Folder 184: 4)
          - 1971 (Folder 184: 5)
      - Pamphlets (The Black Uprisings; The Case for a Black Party; Che Guevara on Vietnam and World Revolution; How to Make a Revolution in the U.S.; I Stake My Life!; Liberalism, Ultraleftism or Mass Action; Peaceful Coexistence and World Revolution; Teamster Rebellion; Why Watts Exploded), 1937-1972 (Folder 184: 6)
    - Material about the Socialist Workers Party (Folder 185)
      - General. HUAC/HISC memoranda, photocopies of index card files, list of contacts from Peter Camejo address book, informant's report, and Veterans Administration document, ca. 1954-1974 (Folder 185: 1)
      - HUAC hearing memoranda with exhibit Socialist Workers Party issuances, 1967 (Folder 185: 2)
      - HISC hearing memorandum with exhibit Socialist Workers Party issuances, 1971 (Folder 185: 3)
      - Massachusetts Department of Public Safety Division of Subversive Activities documentation. Massachusetts police reports with accompanying Socialist Workers Party exhibit items, 1969-1971 (Folder 185: 4)
      - Clippings, printed articles, and flyers, ca. 1954-1972 (Folder 185: 5)
  - Society for Cultural Relations between the Peoples of the British Commonwealth and the U.S.S.R. Serial issue (Anglo-Soviet Journal), 1942 (Folder 185: 6)
  - Sons and Daughters [motion picture film]. Printed synopsis, 1967 (Folder 185: 7)
  - Source Catalog. Printed publication, 1971 (Folder 185: 8)
  - South Africa. Flyers, leaflets, circular letters, and press releases, issued by miscellaneous organizations, re solidarity with the people of South Africa, 1969-1973 (Folder 185: 9)
  - South Shore Organization for Human Rights [Chicago]. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 185: 10)
  - South Side Citizens Defense Committee [Los Angeles]. Press releases and circular letter, 1965-1966 (Folder 185: 11)
  - Southern California Peace Crusade. Letters, leaflets, flyers, newsletters, press releases, pamphlet (Report from China), and statement of dissolution, 1953-1956 (Folder 185: 12)
  - Southern Californians to Abolish HUAC. Circular letter and flyer, 1966 (Folder 185: 13)